<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resource-packs on SHRUB Coop</title>
    <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/resource-packs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resource-packs on SHRUB Coop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.shrubcoop.org/resource-packs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabric Awareness Information Booklet</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/resource-packs/fabric-awareness-information-booklet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/resource-packs/fabric-awareness-information-booklet/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered about the textiles your clothes are made from? Do you know which fibers are natural and which are synthetic?
This booklet should help you to know a bit more about different kinds of fibres and the pros and cons of each. There is a lot more information out there than just in this book so feel free to do your own research and make your own decisions about what you want to support/buy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Set Up a Swap Shop</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/resource-packs/how-to-set-up-a-swap-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/resource-packs/how-to-set-up-a-swap-shop/</guid>
      <description>The aim of this guide is to help you set up a swap shop in an already existing community space.
A swap shop can be a great way of bringing a community together as it encourages swapping between people within the community. It can be really nice when you find something new, to hear about the story of where it came from, and it can often be easier to part with things if you know where they are going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Run a Clothes Swap</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/resource-packs/clothes-swap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/resource-packs/clothes-swap/</guid>
      <description>This guide is designed to give you all of the information you need to set up your own Clothes Swap.
If you would like to come along to one of our events so that we can show you how we run things, please get in touch. If you would like someone to come and help run a clothes swap with you in your venue, this can be organised for a fee that will reflect the staff hours required.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>