<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on SHRUB Coop</title>
    <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on SHRUB Coop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 17:40:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.shrubcoop.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero Waste Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/zero-waste-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/zero-waste-hub/</guid>
      <description>The Zero Waste Hub is your one stop shop for sustainable living!
You can swap your preloved things in our Swapshop, enjoy some rescued food from our Food Sharing Hub, or just hang out and grab a tea or coffee from our cafe.
Opening Hours Wednesday, Thursday, Friday and Saturday
12pm - 5pm
About the Swapshop In the Swapshop you can swap, donate or buy affordable and high quality preloved clothing, books, shoes, bric-a-brac and household items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wee Spoke Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/wee-spoke-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/wee-spoke-hub/</guid>
      <description>The Wee Spoke Hub is a welcoming workshop space where our volunteers and mechanic will help you learn the skills to take care of your bike.
Tools and expertise are provided and participants are welcome to donate what they can.
Simply bring your bike along to one of our Fix Your Own Bike workshops on Tuesday and Thursday evenings, 5-8pm, and our team will check it over and guide you in any repairs it needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Sharing Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/food-sharing-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 17:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/food-sharing-hub/</guid>
      <description>The Food Sharing Hub is Scotland’s first rescued food shop and exists to save surplus food from supermarkets from an unnecessary fate in the bin.
Simply come along to the Food Sharing Hub and sign up as a member of SHRUB Coop for as little as £1 a month. As a member you can fill one basket of food per day and pay as you feel.
How it works The Food Sharing Hub is working with Tesco, Co-op and Waitrose to collect food from 6 local supermarkets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swapshop</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/swapshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 14:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/swapshop/</guid>
      <description>Swap, donate or buy affordable and high quality preloved clothing, books, shoes, bags, bric-a-brac and household items.
Anyone is welcome to buy or donate items. Become a member and you can swap your items in exchange for tokens to use in-store.
How It Works Our vision is for a world without waste. Choosing second hand helps to save carbon emissions and supports a sustainable lifestyle.
Unlike your ordinary charity shop, when you donate your preloved items we give you back 25% of their value as tokens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHRUB Space</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/shrub-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/shrub-space/</guid>
      <description>SHRUB hosts a variety of events and workshops throughout the year, both in our dedicated SHRUB Space workshop space, and in the Zero Waste Hub. Click the &amp;ldquo;Events&amp;rdquo; link at the top to see our upcoming events and workshops and get inspired!
FAQs Do I need to be a member to join? No - anyone can join! For events with a ticket fee, we offer our members a discount.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Opportunity: Swapshop retail coordinator</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/swapshop-retail-coordinator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/swapshop-retail-coordinator/</guid>
      <description>Salary £22,800 p.a. pro rata Part time 8 hours / week (£5,211)
Fixed term contract to 31 March 2020 - extension subject to successful funding bids
Saturdays 11-6pm and two monthly meetings during weekdays
Application Deadline: midnight Tuesday 1st October
Job Purpose
The Swapshop Retail Coordinator works closely alongside the Zero Waste Hub Coordinator in overseeing the Swapshop stock rotation and the retail aspects of the Swapshop, to increase the appeal of the shop to customers and members of the community and shift more items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Opportunity: Wee Spoke Hub Mechanic</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/wee-spoke-hub-mechanic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/wee-spoke-hub-mechanic/</guid>
      <description>Salary £22,800 p.a pro rata (£7,165), part time 11 hours / week
Tuesdays, Wednesdays and Thursdays 5-8.30pm
Fixed term contract to 31 March 2020 – extension subject to successful funding bids
Application Deadline: end of day 6th October
An exciting opportunity has arisen to join the staff team at SHRUB Coop! We’re looking for a bike mechanic to help us run our weekly fix-your-own-bike sessions and help our community to learn how to take care of their bikes, as well as empowering our Wee Spoke Hub volunteers to take ownership of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Opportunity: Café Coordinator</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/cafe-coordinator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/cafe-coordinator/</guid>
      <description>Salary £22,800 p.a. Full time 35 hours / week.
Fixed term contract to 31 March 2020 – extension subject to successful funding bids
Application Deadline: midnight Sunday 29th September
An exciting opportunity has arisen to join the staff team at SHRUB Coop! We’re looking for someone who’s pro-active, passionate about the environment and has a background in hospitality, to develop our Zero Waste Cafe and create a template that other’s can replicate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 things we learned from our quarterly membership survey!</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/membership-survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/membership-survey/</guid>
      <description>We care about our SHRUB community, which is why every three months the Monitoring and Evaluation group asks to hear your concerns, ideas and suggestions through our Quarterly Member Survey. This time we only get 10 responses (we can do better than that next time!) but they were priceless.
1. There are clear positive behavioral changes from being a member. 40% of you reported you throw away less food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making sustainable fashion choices in Edinburgh</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/making-sustainable-fashion-choices-in-edinburgh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/making-sustainable-fashion-choices-in-edinburgh/</guid>
      <description>“Out with the old and in with the new” is the mantra that crops up at this time of year, but this optimistic phrase is deceptively damaging to our world. Wardrobe revamps have become part of the regenerative symbol of spring, leaving a trail of poisonous dyes and discarded fabrics behind them.
The clothing industry has a huge carbon footprint – it takes around 8000 litres of water to produce just one pair of blue jeans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How you can help to reduce food waste in Edinburgh</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/how-you-can-help-to-reduce-food-waste-in-edinburgh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/how-you-can-help-to-reduce-food-waste-in-edinburgh/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that almost a third of all food produced globally is thrown away? In Edinburgh alone, more than 27 tonnes of edible food are thrown out every week – that’s equivalent to 54,000 meals.
Some of this wasted food is thrown out by households and individuals: you can find advice on reducing your own food waste footprint from Love Food, Hate Waste among others.
Most of it, however, is thrown away by supermarkets who are cannot sell perfectly edible food after its ‘Best Before’ date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Bicycle Matters</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/welcome-to-bicycle-matters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/welcome-to-bicycle-matters/</guid>
      <description>The Bicycle Matters Events programme is here!
Over the next few months we’ll be hosting a range of events and workshops to focus on the waste materials from abandoned bikes in an effort to find new creative uses for them.
For this series of Material Matters, we have in store for you:
 Tailored bicycle repair sessions, with our friends at the Wee Spoke Hub – to get old bikes back on the road and save them from going to waste Thought provoking bicycle-themed film screenings – enjoy some free popcorn and let your imagination run (or ride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/volunteer/view/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/volunteer/view/</guid>
      <description>Please send an e-mail to volunteering@shrubcoop.org with a short explanation of why you are interested in this role and any relevant experience you may have. Please put the name of the volunteer roles in the subject of your email.
After receiving your application, we will ask you to come in for an informal chat about the role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sustainable Fashion Meetup Group</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/sustainable-fashion-meetup-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/sustainable-fashion-meetup-group/</guid>
      <description>The fashion industry is now the second most polluting industry in the world after oil.
If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in learning more about the environmental impacts of our fashion habits and want to help develop sustainable fashion ideas in Edinburgh, then come along and get involved with SHRUB Coop&amp;rsquo;s Sustainable Fashion working group!
In our first meet-up, we discussed challenges and solutions to the current fast-fashion industry and planned some exciting projects ahead!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/about-us/</guid>
      <description>We’re a cooperative in Edinburgh working for a world without waste!
We empower our community to live a low carbon life. Become a member and learn to fix a bike, swap your preloved things, enjoy some rescued food and be inspired by new ideas.
Our Purpose  To provide a welcoming space for rethinking our relationship to waste, reducing consumption and developing effective use of resources To support community empowerment in Edinburgh, learning and sharing skills to make a practical difference to the world we share To deliver innovative waste prevention, creative reuse and repair practices in a living laboratory of Circular Economy  Our Values We value inclusivity and work with others to provide a welcoming community for all</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>Enquiries &amp;amp; space booking 0131 220 1884
hello@shrubcoop.org
Zero Waste Hub 12pm to 5pm, Wednesday to Saturday
22 Bread Street, EH3 9AF
0131 281 0583
Wee Spoke Hub 5pm to 8pm, Tuesdays and Wednesdays
13 Guthrie Street, EH1 1JG
0131 220 1884
SHRUB Space &amp;amp; Zero Waste Edinburgh Office 17 Guthrie Street, EH1 1JG
0131 261 8216
info.zwe@shrubcoop.org</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix your own bike workshop</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/fix-your-own-bike-sessions-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/fix-your-own-bike-sessions-1/</guid>
      <description>The Wee Spoke Hub is a welcoming workshop space where our volunteers and mechanic will help you learn the skills to take care of your bike.
We also have a range of refurbished bikes and used parts for sale.
Come along to the Fix Your Own Bike workshops on Tuesdays &amp;amp; Thursdays, 5pm - 8pm.
How It Works Simply bring your bike along to one of our Fix Your Own Bike workshops and our team will check it over and guide you in any repairs it needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix your own bike workshop</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/fix-your-own-bike-workshop-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/fix-your-own-bike-workshop-1/</guid>
      <description>The Wee Spoke Hub is a welcoming workshop space where our volunteers and mechanic will help you learn the skills to take care of your bike.
We also have a range of refurbished bikes and used parts for sale.
Come along to the Fix Your Own Bike workshops on Tuesdays &amp;amp; Thursdays, 5pm - 8pm.
How It Works Simply bring your bike along to one of our Fix Your Own Bike workshops and our team will check it over and guide you in any repairs it needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix your own bike workshop</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/fix-your-own-bike-workshop-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/fix-your-own-bike-workshop-2/</guid>
      <description>The Wee Spoke Hub is a welcoming workshop space where our volunteers and mechanic will help you learn the skills to take care of your bike.
We also have a range of refurbished bikes and used parts for sale.
Come along to the Fix Your Own Bike workshops on Tuesdays &amp;amp; Thursdays, 5pm - 8pm.
How It Works Simply bring your bike along to one of our Fix Your Own Bike workshops and our team will check it over and guide you in any repairs it needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix your own bike workshop</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/fix-your-own-bike-workshop-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/fix-your-own-bike-workshop-3/</guid>
      <description>The Wee Spoke Hub is a welcoming workshop space where our volunteers and mechanic will help you learn the skills to take care of your bike.
We also have a range of refurbished bikes and used parts for sale.
Come along to the Fix Your Own Bike workshops on Tuesdays &amp;amp; Thursdays, 5pm - 8pm.
How It Works Simply bring your bike along to one of our Fix Your Own Bike workshops and our team will check it over and guide you in any repairs it needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix your own bike workshop</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/fix-your-own-bike-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/fix-your-own-bike-workshop/</guid>
      <description>The Wee Spoke Hub is a welcoming workshop space where our volunteers and mechanic will help you learn the skills to take care of your bike.
We also have a range of refurbished bikes and used parts for sale.
Come along to the Fix Your Own Bike workshops on Tuesdays &amp;amp; Thursdays, 5pm - 8pm.
How It Works Simply bring your bike along to one of our Fix Your Own Bike workshops and our team will check it over and guide you in any repairs it needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Involved</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/get-involved/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/get-involved/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Members&#39; Decision Making Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/members-decision-making-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/members-decision-making-meeting/</guid>
      <description>As a member you&amp;rsquo;re welcome to take part in how our organisation is run! Every 4 weeks we meet with ordinaty members, volunteers, staff and representatives from all our working groups for updates on whats going on across the coop.
Everybody is welcome and you don&amp;rsquo;t need to be an expert in any of the proposals up for discussion and you don&amp;rsquo;t need to have attended a meeting before. Simply come along, listen to the ideas and let us know what you think of them to help us make the best choices we can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New &amp; Old Members Warm Welcome!</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/big-swap-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/big-swap-test/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in volunteering for SHRUB, become a paying member or simply want to find out more about what SHRUB is all about?
There is a lot to us so whether you are brand new or have been around a while come along and get informed.
Come join other like-minded people, learn a bit about what we do and how we work and discover what volunteer experiences might be available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New &amp; Old Members Warm Welcome!</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/new-old-members-warm-welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/new-old-members-warm-welcome/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in volunteering for SHRUB, become a paying member or simply want to find out more about what SHRUB is all about?
There is a lot to us so whether you are brand new or have been around a while come along and get informed.
Come join other like-minded people, learn a bit about what we do and how we work and discover what volunteer experiences might be available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thursday night sewing sessions</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/thursday-night-sewing-sessions-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/thursday-night-sewing-sessions-1/</guid>
      <description>Are you itching to start any sewing projects? Have you got a well loved item of clothing you want to mend? Come along to our sewing drop-in sessions!
We&amp;rsquo;re opening the doors to our workshop space each week for people of all sewing abilities to meet and get advice.
So whether you&amp;rsquo;ve got an upcycling project in mind, need to repair or alter something, or want to just join us for a cup of tea, drop by!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thursday night sewing sessions</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/thursday-night-sewing-sessions-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/thursday-night-sewing-sessions-2/</guid>
      <description>Are you itching to start any sewing projects? Have you got a well loved item of clothing you want to mend? Come along to our sewing drop-in sessions!
We&amp;rsquo;re opening the doors to our workshop space each week for people of all sewing abilities to meet and get advice.
So whether you&amp;rsquo;ve got an upcycling project in mind, need to repair or alter something, or want to just join us for a cup of tea, drop by!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thursday night sewing sessions</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/thursday-night-sewing-sessions-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/thursday-night-sewing-sessions-3/</guid>
      <description>Are you itching to start any sewing projects? Have you got a well loved item of clothing you want to mend? Come along to our sewing drop-in sessions!
We&amp;rsquo;re opening the doors to our workshop space each week for people of all sewing abilities to meet and get advice.
So whether you&amp;rsquo;ve got an upcycling project in mind, need to repair or alter something, or want to just join us for a cup of tea, drop by!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thursday night sewing sessions</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/thursday-night-sewing-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/thursday-night-sewing-sessions/</guid>
      <description>Are you itching to start any sewing projects? Have you got a well loved item of clothing you want to mend? Come along to our sewing drop-in sessions!
We&amp;rsquo;re opening the doors to our workshop space each week for people of all sewing abilities to meet and get advice.
So whether you&amp;rsquo;ve got an upcycling project in mind, need to repair or alter something, or want to just join us for a cup of tea, drop by!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero Waste Festival</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/another-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/events/another-event/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to a family friendly, weekend celebration of all things zero waste!
We&amp;rsquo;ll be hosting a collection of upcycling workshops, stalls of zero waste activities, and live entertainment.
We&amp;rsquo;ll also be holding a clothes swap! So bring along your pre-loved items and take home something else!
On Saturday evening (6pm), join us for a selection of family friendly short environmental films provided by Take One Action Film Festivals
On Sunday evening (7pm till late), join us for an afterparty at Henry&amp;rsquo;s Cellar Bar with Electric Alpaca</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>