<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on SHRUB Coop</title>
    <link>https://shrub.space/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on SHRUB Coop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://shrub.space/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Opportunity: Wee Spoke Hub Mechanic</title>
      <link>https://shrub.space/news/wee-spoke-hub-mechanic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrub.space/news/wee-spoke-hub-mechanic/</guid>
      <description>Salary £22,800 p.a pro rata (£7,165), part time 11 hours / week
Tuesdays, Wednesdays and Thursdays 5-8.30pm
Fixed term contract to 31 March 2020 – extension subject to successful funding bids
Application Deadline: end of day 6th October
An exciting opportunity has arisen to join the staff team at SHRUB Coop! We’re looking for a bike mechanic to help us run our weekly fix-your-own-bike sessions and help our community to learn how to take care of their bikes, as well as empowering our Wee Spoke Hub volunteers to take ownership of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Opportunity: Café Coordinator</title>
      <link>https://shrub.space/news/cafe-coordinator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrub.space/news/cafe-coordinator/</guid>
      <description>Salary £22,800 p.a. Full time 35 hours / week.
Fixed term contract to 31 March 2020 – extension subject to successful funding bids
Application Deadline: midnight Sunday 29th September
An exciting opportunity has arisen to join the staff team at SHRUB Coop! We’re looking for someone who’s pro-active, passionate about the environment and has a background in hospitality, to develop our Zero Waste Cafe and create a template that other’s can replicate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 things we learned from our quarterly membership survey!</title>
      <link>https://shrub.space/news/membership-survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrub.space/news/membership-survey/</guid>
      <description>We care about our SHRUB community, which is why every three months the Monitoring and Evaluation group asks to hear your concerns, ideas and suggestions through our Quarterly Member Survey. This time we only get 10 responses (we can do better than that next time!) but they were priceless.
1. There are clear positive behavioral changes from being a member. 40% of you reported you throw away less food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making sustainable fashion choices in Edinburgh</title>
      <link>https://shrub.space/news/making-sustainable-fashion-choices-in-edinburgh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrub.space/news/making-sustainable-fashion-choices-in-edinburgh/</guid>
      <description>“Out with the old and in with the new” is the mantra that crops up at this time of year, but this optimistic phrase is deceptively damaging to our world. Wardrobe revamps have become part of the regenerative symbol of spring, leaving a trail of poisonous dyes and discarded fabrics behind them.
The clothing industry has a huge carbon footprint – it takes around 8000 litres of water to produce just one pair of blue jeans.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>