<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Shrub Co-op</title>
    <link>https://shrubcoop.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Shrub Co-op</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 15:34:58 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://shrubcoop.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Swapshop</title>
      <link>https://shrubcoop.org/working-groups/swapshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrubcoop.org/working-groups/swapshop/</guid>
      <description>Our Swapshop and Freeshop projects are run for the community to save waste and stop items being sent to landfill.
We estimate that it has saved over 75 tons of items from landfill over the past 10 years,with last year saving over 15 tons!
The Swapshop allows people to Buy items for cash or Shrub-Tokens in store: volunteers will check cash values by looking up the cheapest online price and using this as a guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Sharing</title>
      <link>https://shrubcoop.org/working-groups/food-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrubcoop.org/working-groups/food-sharing/</guid>
      <description>What is food sharing all about? Food Sharing Edinburgh was established in Edinburgh in late 2013, and is now rapidly expanding, based on a very similar concept operating in Germany.
The Food Sharing project connects people so they can exchange their excess food instead of throwing it away and wasting it.
Volunteers can collect food from businesses and redistribute it around the community to friends, family, neighbours, charities, poor, homeless and shelters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wee Spoke Hub</title>
      <link>https://shrubcoop.org/working-groups/wee-spoke-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrubcoop.org/working-groups/wee-spoke-hub/</guid>
      <description>What even is a bike? A bicycle, also called a cycle or bike, is a human-powered or motor-powered, pedal-driven, single-track vehicle, having two wheels attached to a frame, one behind the other. A bicycle rider is called a cyclist, or bicyclist.
Bicycles were introduced in the late 19th century in Europe, and by the early 21st century, more than 1 billion have been produced worldwide. These numbers far exceed the number of cars, both in total and ranked by the number of individual models produced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>https://shrubcoop.org/working-groups/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrubcoop.org/working-groups/workshops/</guid>
      <description>We host workshops to teach such skills as how to make:
 Wallets out of bicycle inner tubes or tetra pacs Hula hoops out of water piping Chandeliers out of bicycle wheels Jewellery out of bicycle inner tubes or paper Backyard wind turbines out of aluminium printing sheets Mudguards out of plastic bottles.  … and much more!
As well as the practical workshops, we host inspiring discussions and talks about environmental and social issues related to climate change, activism, waste and social justice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cineshrub</title>
      <link>https://shrubcoop.org/working-groups/cineshrub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrubcoop.org/working-groups/cineshrub/</guid>
      <description>Cineshrub shows films sometimes about social justice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Beginnings</title>
      <link>https://shrubcoop.org/blog/new-beginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 15:34:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrubcoop.org/blog/new-beginnings/</guid>
      <description>This is a post all about the new swapshop and the stuff we gone and did!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our New Swapshop!</title>
      <link>https://shrubcoop.org/blog/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 15:34:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrubcoop.org/blog/first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is a post all about the new swapshop and the stuff we gone and did!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://shrubcoop.org/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrubcoop.org/about-us/</guid>
      <description>SHRUB is a thing!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://shrubcoop.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrubcoop.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email us at shrub@shrubcoop.org</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Involved</title>
      <link>https://shrubcoop.org/get-involved/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrubcoop.org/get-involved/</guid>
      <description>Volunteer with us!
Sign up to our news letter!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHRUB Relaunch Party!</title>
      <link>https://shrubcoop.org/events/first-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrubcoop.org/events/first-event/</guid>
      <description>SHRUB has evolved - right now is a really exciting time in our history, we&amp;rsquo;ve just expanded to our new location on Bread Street, opened a new upcycling workshop, and reinvented the Wee Spoke Hub.
We&amp;rsquo;ve organised an evening of speakers and live entertainment, as well as interactive stalls showcasing our different projects.
There will be&amp;hellip; Upcycling activities, DIY bike maintenance advice from the The Wee Spoke Hub, Nibbles provided by Food Sharing Edinburgh, and refreshments available from the brand new SHRUB Café!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>