<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Working-groups on SHRUB Coop</title>
    <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Working-groups on SHRUB Coop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 17:40:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero Waste Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/zero-waste-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/zero-waste-hub/</guid>
      <description>The Zero Waste Hub is your one stop shop for sustainable living!
You can swap your preloved things in our Swapshop, enjoy some rescued food from our Food Sharing Hub, or just hang out and grab a tea or coffee from our vegetarian and vegan café.
Our café serves a range of wholesome vegan sandwiches, soups, and cakes. Heartwarming coffee with no extra charge for non-dairy milks!
Say No To Disposable Cups!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wee Spoke Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/wee-spoke-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/wee-spoke-hub/</guid>
      <description>The Wee Spoke Hub is a welcoming workshop space where tools and expertise are provided by our volunteers and mechanic to help you learn the skills to take care of your bike.
We have a range of refurbished bikes and second hand parts for sale and we are currently available for bike repair bookings so drop our wonderful Mechanic, Anna, an email to arrange a slot at weespokehub@shrubcoop.org or call on 0131 358 3637.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Sharing Edinburgh</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/food-sharing-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 17:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/food-sharing-hub/</guid>
      <description>Each year, one-third of all food produced for human consumption worldwide goes to waste. This is approximately 1.3 billion tonnes. (FAO, 2019). In central Edinburgh, 27.1 tonnes of food goes to waste every week - that&amp;rsquo;s the equivalent of roughly 54,000 meals unnecessarily thrown in the bin (Zero Waste Edinburgh, 2017).
The Food Sharing Hub, located in our Zero Waste Hub at 22 Bread Street, is Scotland’s first rescued food shop and exists to save surplus food from supermarkets and small businesses around Edinburgh from an unnecessary fate in the bin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swapshop</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/swapshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 14:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/swapshop/</guid>
      <description>Swap, donate or buy affordable and high quality preloved clothing, books, shoes, bags, bric-a-brac and household items.
Anyone is welcome to buy or donate items. Become a member and you can swap your items in exchange for tokens to use in-store.
How It Works Our vision is for a world without waste. Choosing second hand helps to save carbon emissions and supports a sustainable lifestyle.
Unlike your ordinary charity shop, when you donate your preloved items we give you back 20% of their value as tokens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHRUB Space</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/shrub-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/shrub-space/</guid>
      <description>SHRUB hosts a variety of events and workshops throughout the year, both in our dedicated SHRUB Space workshop space, and in the Zero Waste Hub. Click the &amp;ldquo;Events&amp;rdquo; link at the top to see our upcoming events and workshops and get inspired!
Frequently Asked Questions Do I need to be a member to join? No - anyone can join! For events with a ticket fee, we offer our members a discount.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>