<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Working-groups on SHRUB Coop</title>
    <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Working-groups on SHRUB Coop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 17:40:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero Waste Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/zero-waste-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/zero-waste-hub/</guid>
      <description>The Zero Waste Hub is your one stop shop for sustainable living!
You can swap your preloved things in our Swapshop, enjoy some rescued food from our Food Sharing Hub, or just hang out and grab a tea or coffee from our vegetarian and vegan café.
Our café serves a range of wholesome vegan sandwiches, soups, and cakes. Heartwarming coffee with no extra charge for non-dairy milks!
Say No To Disposable Cups!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wee Spoke Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/wee-spoke-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/wee-spoke-hub/</guid>
      <description>The Wee Spoke Hub is a welcoming workshop space where tools and expertise are provided by our volunteers and mechanic to help you learn the skills to take care of your bike.
We also have a range of refurbished bikes and second hand parts for sale. As a member of SHRUB Coop you get discounts on parts.
We are starting to reopen our doors to the public following some new incoming funding and Covid-19 safety adjustments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Sharing Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/food-sharing-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 17:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/food-sharing-hub/</guid>
      <description>The Food Sharing Hub is Scotland’s first rescued food shop and exists to save surplus food from supermarkets from an unnecessary fate in the bin.
It&amp;rsquo;s open for everyone. Simply come along to the Food Sharing Hub. Fill a basket with food and pay as you feel.
How it works The Food Sharing Hub is working with Tesco, Co-op and Waitrose to collect food from 6 local supermarkets. Volunteers collect perishable foods such as fruit, vegetables, and baked goods that are still fresh and good to eat, but have passed their best before dates and would otherwise be thrown out that day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swapshop</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/swapshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 14:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/swapshop/</guid>
      <description>Swap, donate or buy affordable and high quality preloved clothing, books, shoes, bags, bric-a-brac and household items.
Anyone is welcome to buy or donate items. Become a member and you can swap your items in exchange for tokens to use in-store.
How It Works Our vision is for a world without waste. Choosing second hand helps to save carbon emissions and supports a sustainable lifestyle.
Unlike your ordinary charity shop, when you donate your preloved items we give you back 20% of their value as tokens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SHRUB Space</title>
      <link>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/shrub-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.shrubcoop.org/working-groups/shrub-space/</guid>
      <description>SHRUB hosts a variety of events and workshops throughout the year, both in our dedicated SHRUB Space workshop space, and in the Zero Waste Hub. Click the &amp;ldquo;Events&amp;rdquo; link at the top to see our upcoming events and workshops and get inspired!
Frequently Asked Questions Do I need to be a member to join? No - anyone can join! For events with a ticket fee, we offer our members a discount.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>