<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on SHRUB Coop</title>
    <link>https://shrub.space/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on SHRUB Coop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://shrub.space/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Sustainable Fashion Meetup Group</title>
      <link>https://shrub.space/events/sustainable-fashion-meetup-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrub.space/events/sustainable-fashion-meetup-group/</guid>
      <description>The fashion industry is now the second most polluting industry in the world after oil.
If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in learning more about the environmental impacts of our fashion habits and want to help develop sustainable fashion ideas in Edinburgh, then come along and get involved with SHRUB Coop&amp;rsquo;s Sustainable Fashion working group!
In our first meet-up, we discussed challenges and solutions to the current fast-fashion industry and planned some exciting projects ahead!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New &amp; Old Members Warm Welcome!</title>
      <link>https://shrub.space/events/big-swap-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrub.space/events/big-swap-test/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in volunteering for SHRUB, become a paying member or simply want to find out more about what SHRUB is all about?
There is a lot to us so whether you are brand new or have been around a while come along and get informed.
Come join other like-minded people, learn a bit about what we do and how we work and discover what volunteer experiences might be available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero Waste Festival</title>
      <link>https://shrub.space/events/another-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shrub.space/events/another-event/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to a family friendly, weekend celebration of all things zero waste!
We&amp;rsquo;ll be hosting a collection of upcycling workshops, stalls of zero waste activities, and live entertainment.
We&amp;rsquo;ll also be holding a clothes swap! So bring along your pre-loved items and take home something else!
On Saturday evening (6pm), join us for a selection of family friendly short environmental films provided by Take One Action Film Festivals
On Sunday evening (7pm till late), join us for an afterparty at Henry&amp;rsquo;s Cellar Bar with Electric Alpaca</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>